paydayfinders.co.uk 2009-04-15

# UK Cash Loans

The following policy explains how we gather and use personal information in detail. This policy may change from time to time and PayDayFinders reserves the right to change or modify this policy at any time with or without notice. If you have any questions about this policy, please feel free to contact us.

By using this Site, you agree that you will be registered with PayDayFinders, and that you accept this Privacy Policy. You will not be registered merely by visiting the Site; you will only be registered if you affirmatively click on one of the Site's options to directly match you with a loan or provide other services. Also, by providing us with your personal information on our Site or in the course of using our services, you consent to the transfer of your Personal Data and Sensitive Personal Data, and any other data we acquire about you from third-party service providers in the process of evaluating you for a loan, to companies outside the EU, including but not limited to, the Network Sites and other consumer credit lenders and their affiliates. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you should not use this Site. If you have already registered and wish to terminate your registration, follow the instructions in "Opting-Out of Further Communications," below.

Registration:  
PayDayFinders only collects personally identifiable information ("PII") that is volunteered during the registration process or in response to specific information requests. Examples of PII that may be requested include: first and last name, address, email address, and telephone number. Anybody completing and submitting any of the forms (including our newsletter) on the PayDayFinders domain is considered a "registrant." In addition, PayDayFinders may collect your IP address and information through use of electronic "cookies."

When you register with PayDayFinders you automatically consent to registration in all the other online properties in the PayDayFinders network (collectively, the "Network Sites"). Accordingly, PayDayFinders may share registrant PII with the Network Sites.

Use and Sharing of PII  
PayDayFinders reserves the right to use registrant PII: (1) for the specific purpose for which such information was provided (including matching registrants with a cash advance loan company or companies); (2) as disclosed at the time such information is provided; and (3) as disclosed in this Policy. However, please note that PayDayFinders may change this Policy at any time and therefore PayDayFinders may in the future use registrant PII for additional purposes not currently included in this Policy.

Also, PayDayFinders may share registrant PII with its partners, sponsors, advertisers, unaffiliated third-party consumer credit lenders, service providers and marketers' lookup and reference services and any other entities that PayDayFinders believes are able to provide registrants with special offers and opportunities. Note that although PayDayFinders advises, PayDayFinders has no control over such party's information handling practices and is not responsible for any failure of such party to adhere to this Policy.

As a condition of registration, registrants agree that PayDayFinders may share their PII with the Network Sites and unaffiliated third parties. If you do not agree that PayDayFinders may share your PII with such entities, you may not register on PayDayFinders, and if you are already registered, you must immediately terminate your account, by following the instructions in "Opting-Out of Further Communications."

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including wireless services that display customized content and advertising. In addition to any fee of which you are notified, your provider's standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS correspondence. You may opt-out and remove your SMS information by sending "STOP", "END", "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received. If you remove your SMS information from our database it will no longer be used by us for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by us or third parties to send promotional correspondence to you.

Additionally, PayDayFinders may share Registrant PII in aggregate, non-personal form, with select companies that wish to reach a particular target audience. This information will allow these entities to provide relevant offers to specific registrants.

Finally, PayDayFinders may disclose registrant PII in order to: (1) comply with applicable laws; (2) respond to governmental inquiries; (3) comply with valid legal process; and (4) protect the rights or property of PayDayFinders, the Network Sites or other registrants of this Site.

Do Not Call Registry Compliance:  
By submitting personal contact and/or financial information through PayDayFinders, the user hereby grants written permission to PayDayFinders, its affiliated sites, and its business partners for contact via telephone, mail, and/or e-mail. Further, by registering at PayDayFinders you are consenting to receive phone calls from PayDayFinders, its affiliated sites, and its business partners for contact via telephone, including but not limited to lenders that may contact you regarding a loan and thereby registrants waive their right to file a claim with the FTC or any other agency in reference to these calls or contacts.

Third Party Offers:  
By registering at PayDayFinders you may receive follow-up contacts/offers from third party companies. We cannot be responsible for the services or representations of third party advertisers.

Links to Other Sites:  
PayDayFinders contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

Security, Fraud, and Abuse:  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. PayDayFinders regularly reviews these measures to better protect you.

Opting-Out of Further Communications:  
PayDayFinders registrants may opt-out of receiving further communications from PayDayFinders. Registrants may, at any time, choose not to receive promotional emails from PayDayFinders or the Network by following the "unsubscribe" instructions in any PayDayFinders e-mail received by registrant.

Note that unsubscribing from one email list does not automatically unsubscribe you from any other email list that you may be on. Please read the email carefully to find out which list you are unsubscribing from.

Must Be 18 Years or Older:  
PayDayFinders or its Network is neither intended for, nor directed to, children under the age of 18. If PayDayFinders learns that a person who registers on the Site is under the age of 18, PayDayFinders will promptly delete that individual's registration.

Transfer In Certain Circumstances:  
In its sole discretion, PayDayFinders may transfer, sell or assign information collected on and through this Site, including without limitation, PII and other registrant-provided information, to one or more third parties, as a result of the sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of PayDayFinders and/or Network Sites.

Change in Policy:  
PayDayFinders may, from time to time, amend this Policy, in whole or part, in its sole discretion. Depending on the nature of the change, PayDayFinders will either announce the change (1) on the privacy policy page of the site, or (2) provide such notice via e-mail to registrants. By not unsubscribing, following the announcement of any changes, you will be deemed to have agreed to such changes. If you do not agree with the terms of this Policy, as it may be amended from time to time, in whole or part, you must terminate your registration by unsubscribing.

Data Transfer Consent:  
By submitting information on this form, the consumer consents to this data being transferred outside of the UK.

Our Right to Contact You :  
The use of Company web site constitutes an existing business relationship between Company or any of its affiliates with whom Company shares information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. The use of Company web site qualifies as consent to be contacted by, including but not limited to, telephone and email for changes in account status, changes in subscriber agreements, marketing opportunities, privacy policies and/or any other policies or agreements relevant to you or your account.
